The Future Is Present
A.I. Rising is a science fiction, drama, romance film directed by Lazar Bodroža.
On a lonely mission to Alpha Centauri, Milutin is teamed up with Nimani
1345, a female cyborg designed to fulfill his every need.
At first thrilled to be able to control her, Sebastian grows
tired of having his desires fulfilled so easily.
Longing for human intimacy, Sebastian alters Nimani's programmed responses, but
in doing so he risks the mission's security — and his own life.
Milutin, played by Sebastian Cavazza.
Nimani 1345, played by Stoya.
Social Engineer, played by Maruša Majer.
Computer, played by Kirsty Besterman.
Rising (also known as Ederlezi Rising and Ederlezi ébredése) is a 2018 English-language Serbian science fiction film directed by Lazar
Bodroža and based on a 1980s short story by Zoran Nešković that was adapted for film by screenwriter Dimitrije Vojnov.
The film stars Sebastian Cavazza, Stoya, Marusa Majer, and Kirsty Besterman.
The film explores themes of android, artificial intelligence
(a.i.), dystopia, soviet union, space mission.
The tone is emotional and thought_provoking.